advance.net 2007-10-14

# advance.net

**Privacy Policy**

Last Revised August 12, 2002

Kids and parents click here!

In addition to reviewing this privacy policy, please read our User Agreement. Your use of advance.net constitutes agreement to its terms and conditions.

advance.net is produced by Advance Internet, Inc. This policy does not cover information collected on sites linked to from advance.net.

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page, so check back often. Continued access of advance.net by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

It is the goal of advance.net to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy. The following is a summary of the various ways we treat the information you provide us while using our site.

**THE TYPE OF INFORMATION ADVANCE.NET COLLECTS**

advance.net generally collects personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent. For instance, when you send us an e-mail message, you may provide personal identifying information to us.

**HOW ADVANCE.NET USES INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU**

advance.net uses this information to provide you with the service you have requested.

advance.net does not sell our users' e-mail addresses. However, unless otherwise specified, we may share e-mail addresses and sell or share all other information with our affiliates and with carefully selected companies who we think can offer you services and products of interest to you. If you do not wish to have your information shared, write to us at [advance@advance.net](mailto:advance@advance.net). If you do not wish to receive communications from us, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions contained within the e-mail.

While your individual information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.

**IP ADDRESS**

Your Internet Protocol ("IP") address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company or your university. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, gather broad demographic information, and administer our website.

**KIDS AND PARENTS**

advance.net is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s) before making purchases, including subscriptions, on this site.

If you're worried about your children's activities or their privacy on our site, we encourage you to e-mail our Privacy Policy Coordinator at [advance@advance.net](mailto:advance@advance.net).

If you have other concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, you may also e-mail our Privacy Policy Coordinator. We welcome your feedback. You can also send us regular mail at the following address: 

Privacy Policy Coordinator  
Advance Internet  
30 Journal Square  
Jersey City, NJ 07306
